Horlacher, John Arbitration Records 5587
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John Horlacher Arbitration Records
1947-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Horlacher, John Perry
5587
19 cubic feet
19 linear ft.
Papers (documents), records (documents).
Collective labor agreements.
5667697
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 12, 2007
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 20, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial; Collective bargaining; Horlacher, John Perry, 1901-; A.S. Abell Company; American Chain & Cable Company; Allied Chemical Corporation; Atlantic Independent Union; Amoco Chemicals Corporation; BP Oil Corporation; Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania; Budd Company; Celotex Corporation; Food Fair Stores, Inc.; Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania; Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada; Heil Company; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 676; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 1069; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. Local 101; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. Local 102; International Association of Machinists; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Merck & Co.; National Sugar Refining Company; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; New York Shipbuilding Corporation; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation; Philadelphia Inquirer; Philadelphia Newspaper, Inc.; Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Company; Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company; Philco Corporation; Retail Store Employees Union; Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Company; Teleflex, Incorporated; Texaco, Inc.; Transport Workers Union of America. Local 267; Transport Workers Union of America. Local 234; United Papermakers and Paperworkers; United Paperworkers International Union; United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America; United Steelworkers of America; United Steelworkers of America. Local 6880; Upper Southampton Township; Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild; Washington Post Company; Wickes Industries, Inc.; Vertol Division of Boeing Company; Yale & Towne Manufacturing Company
5667697
- ABC Airfreight Co. vs. Teamsters Local 470, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Issue: discharge-misconduct
- ACF Industries, Inc., Shippers Car Line Division, Red House Plant, W. Va. vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1a)
  Issue: discharge - plant rules - refusal to work
- AFC Brill Motors Co. vs. USA, Local 1263, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Issue: claim for pay of higher classification-experimental work
- The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., Inc., vs. Retail Clerks Int'l. Assn., Local 1361, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Issue: inter-union disputes jurisdiction, assignment of jobs - transfer
- The Great A & P Tea Co., Newark Queens Street Bakery vs. Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Union, Local 262 of New Jersey, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Issue: absence -failure to call-in, arbitration procedure, absence of grievant
- AVH Corporation vs. Int'l. Assn. of Machinists, Lodge 2111, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Issue: Overtime-Equalization (AVM Corp. - Jamestown Product Division - see Bx. #9, ff#8)
- Abell, A.S. Co. vs. Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, Local 35, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Issue: discharge-mode of dress (hair)
- Abell, A.S. Co. vs. Baltimore Typographical Union (BTU), Local 12, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Issue: assignment of jobs - supervisors - seniority bidding vs. BTU, Local 12. Hearing date. 3/21. Issue: prior arbitration award (see ff # 6)
- Abell, A.S. Co. vs. Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Issue: vacation pay - strike
- Abell, A.S. Co. vs. Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, Local 35, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Issue: subcontracting - case w/drawn
- Abell, A.S. Co. vs. Baltimore Typographical Union 12, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Issue: discharge - negligence.
- Abell, A.S. Co. vs. Baltimore Newspaper Web and Pressmen's Union, Local 31 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Issue: layoff as discipline.
- Abex Corp. (Meadville PA Plant) vs. Int'l. Assn. of Machinists & Aerospace Workers (IAM) Local Lodge 1385, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Issue: discharge - absences -reporting.
- ACE Lumber & Millwork Co. vs. General Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Helpers & Yardmen, Local 470, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Issue: discharge - accident proneness.
- Acker Drill Co., Inc. vs. IAM, Local 1971, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Issue: discharge - improper job attitude & unsatisfactory work.
- ACME Fast Freight, Inc. vs. Brotherhood. of Railway, Airline & Steamship Clerks, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Issue: failure to bid - status.
- ACHE Markets, Inc. Cases, 1964-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- AO-Plate, Inc. and Philadelphia Lithographers and Photoengravers Int'l. Union, Local 7-p. 1) 5/5/72. Issue: interpretation of prior award, reduction of work week. 2), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Issue: layoff - super seniority
- Air Products & Chemicals, Inc. vs. IAM Lodges, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Airce Speer Carbon - Graphite Products vs. Int'l. Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers., Local 502, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Issue: wildcat strike - discipline - union representatives.
- Alkon Products Corp. vs. UAW, Local 669, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Issue: discipline - discrimination.
- Allen Products Co., Inc. vs. Teamsters Local 773, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Issue: bidding - seniority.
- Allentown Portland Cement Co. vs. United Cement, Lime & Gypsum Workers. Int'l. Union, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Allied Chemical Corp. Cases, 1967-1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Issues: Temporary Employees, elimination of jobs.
- Allied Chemical Corp., Agricultural Div., Baltimore Plant vs. UHW, Local 12388, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Issue: assignment of jobs -failure to assign - overtime.
- Allied Chemical Corp., Delaware Works vs. USA, Local Union 12781, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Issue: assignment to work outside classification.
- Allied Printing Employers Assn. and Philadelphia Typographical Union 2, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Issue: rates of pay.
- Altenpohl, W.F., Inc. vs. IBT Local 384, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Issue: suspension - unsatisfactory work, disloyalty, insubordination; vacation scheduling.
- American Baptist Board of Education & Publication vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union 2, Int'l. Typographical Union, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Issue: refusing to grant training.
- American Can Co. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers (UPP) Local Union 412, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Issue: multiple grievance arbitrations.
- American Chain & Cable Co. vs. USA, CIO, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Issue: incentive pay, unsatisfactory work - standards of production; discharge - absences - reporting; rates of pay - incentive pay - retroactive; incentive pay - change of operations.
- American Chain & Cable Co., Inc. vs. USA, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- American Radiator & Standard Sanitary Corp. vs. UAW, Local 344, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Issue: rate of pay - piecework v. Daywork; rates of pay incentive pay (piece rate) - increase.
- American Standard, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pottery & Allied Workers, Local 175, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Issue: rate of pay - change of operations.
- American Sugar Co. vs. Sugar Refinery Workers, Local 1650, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Issue: assignment of jobs, elimination of jobs, net equipment; rate of pay automation added duties.
- Amoco Chemicals Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Int'l. Union, (OCAW), Local 8-732, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  Issue: overtime equalization; discharge insubordination prior record.
- Amoco Chemicals Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Int'l. Union, (OCAW), Local 8-732, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Issue: rate of pay, claim for pay of a higher classification - change of operations.
- Amoco Chemicals Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Int'l. Union, (OCAW), Local 8-732, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Issue: classification of jobs. No decision (hearings only).
- Amoroso Baking Co. vs. Bakery vs. Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union, Local 6, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Issue: discipline -discharge.
- Amstar Corp.. Philadelphia Refinery vs. Sugar Refinery Workers' Union, Local 1650, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Issue: suspensions - pending court action; classification of jobs change of duties.
- Anchor Motor Freight, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 107, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Issue: rates of pay - Saturday, Sunday & holiday work.
- Armstrong Cork Co., Lancaster Floor Plant vs. IAM, Lodge 928, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Issue: discipline - suspension.
- Arcos Corp. vs. USW, Local 4538, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Associate Concrete Producers, Trap Rock, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 470, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Issue: jurisdiction -assignment of jobs.
- Association of Bricklayers Welfare & Pension Funds, Local 21 Union Trustees, vs. Employer Trustees, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Issue: fringe benefits - pension plans, welfare funds.
- Associated Metalcrafts Co., Inc. vs. IAM, District Lodge 1, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Atlantic Refining Co. vs. Atlantic Independent Union, 1956-1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Atlantic Richfield Co. vs. Atlantic Independent Union, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Atlas Chain Manufacturing vs. UAW, Local 271, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Atlas Chemical Industries, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 401; vs. UMW District 50, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Atlas Provider Co. vs. UMW. District 50, Local 13101, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Issue: management rights - job content.
- Auto Kraft Box Corp. vs. Upholsterers' Int'l. Union of H.A., Local 465, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Issue: overtime -seniority.
- Avco Mfg. Corp., Lycoming Div. vs. AUW, Local 787, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Issue: arbitrability; shutdown - weather conditions.
- Aviation Supply Office, Dept. of Navy, Philadelphia, PA vs. Nat'l. Assoc. of Government Employees, Local R3-36, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Issue: union security - exclusive bargaining rights.
- Avisun Corp. vs. Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers Int'l. Union, Local 8-732 (OCAW), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Issue: discipline suspension; discipline - discharge.
- BP Oil Co. Cases, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Babbitt, B.T., Inc., Curley Division vs. OCAW, Local 8-398, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Issue:
- Babcock and Wilcox Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers & Helpers, Local 904 (IBBISBFH). 4/1/68. Issue: Overtime - shift preference. (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Baker, J.T. Chemical Co. vs. OCAW, Local 8-729, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Issue: vacations - shutdown.
- Baldwin - Lima - Hamilton Corp. vs. USW. Local 1278, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay.
- Baltimore Transit Co. vs. Amalgamated Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of Amer., Division 1300, 1954-1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Issue: suspensions; discipline discharge; theft employee liability for robbery.
- Bardu Farms, Inc. vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1262, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Issue: discipline - negligence & carelessness.
- Barrett, Haentjens & Co. vs. Int'l. Holders & Allied Workers of N. A., Local 422, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Issue: rates of pay - Sat., Sun. & holiday work.
- Baruffi Brothers; Dominic Baruffi vs. Wood, Wire Lathers Int'l. Union, Local 29 (WWML), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Issue: union security - contracting out.
- Bearings Co. of America, division Federal-Mogul Bover Bearings, Inc. vs. USW, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Issue: holidays & holiday pay - rates of pay.
- Beck Engraving Co. vs. Philadelphia Lithographers & Photoengravers Int'l. Union, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Issue: reclassification.
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Issue: 1) assignment of lobs -technological improvements. 2) transfers -involuntary. 3) assignment of jobs - supervisors (includes exhibits, drafts, notes, etc.) 5) transcripts
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Issue: discharge - unsatisfactory work & insubordination (includes transcripts, briefs, notes, drafts.)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Issue: assignment of lobs -technological improvements (exhibits, notes, briefs.)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Fed. of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bellanca Aircraft Corp. vs. United Automobile Workers, CIO (AUW), Local 840, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bellefonte Area School District vs. Bellefonte Area Education Association, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Belmont Iron Works vs. United Steelworkers of American (USW), Local 1390, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Issue: discrimination - transfers; discipline - suspensions; layoffs.
- Bensalen, Township of vs. Police of Bensalem Township, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Issue: interest arbitration.
- Beryllium Corp. vs. USW, CIO, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Issue: overtime. 1/15/58, Issue: posting, vacancies.
- Bethlehem, City of vs. Fraternal Order of Police, Star Lodge No. 20, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Issue: contract modification.
- Bethlehem Contracting Co. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Beverage Lease way, Inc. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Machinists (IAM) Automotive & Body Builders Local Union #724, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Blue Ridge Pressure Castings, Co. vs. UAW, Local 1098, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Issue: vacancies - qualifications. DISMISSED.
- Blumenthal Brothers Chocolate Co. vs. Bakery & Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union, Local 6, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Boiler Engineering & Supply Co., Inc. vs. USW, Local 7004, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Issue: discipline - suspensions.
- Boise Cascade Corp. (Bristol Plant) vs. Int'l. Brotherhood. of Pulp, Sulphite & Paper Mill Workers, Local 286, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Bristol Paper Co. vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Union (UPIU), Local 500, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Issue: classification of jobs - supervisors.
- Bristol Township, School District of vs. Office & Professional Employees Int'l. Union (OPEIU), Local 426, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Issue: contracting out; reinstatement; bumping.
- Brown Co., Bermico Div., Lumberton, N.J. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood. of Sulphite & Paper Mill Workers, Local 286, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Issue: transfers - involuntary.
- Buck Co., Inc. vs. Int'l. Holders' & Allied Workers' Union, Local 287. 1), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Issue: Termination of Employment - discrimination. 2) 8/9/63. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Budd Co. vs. UAW, Local 813, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  1) Issue: bumping - qualifications. 2) Issue: premium pay -Saturday, Sunday & Holiday work. 3) Issue: overtime - assignment of jobs.
- Budd Co. (Huntington Park Plant) vs. Independent Workers Union of the Budd Co, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Issue: reduction in force - bumping, layoff.
- Budd Co., Polychem Division, Newark, DE vs. United Textile Workers of America, Local 266 (UTWA), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Issue: layoff - seniority.
- Burgundy Bar & Restaurant vs. Hotel, Motel & Club Employees Union, Loci 568, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Burns, James F. Co. vs. IAH, Local 159 of Local Lodge 1, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Buzby Bros. & Co., Inc. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Teamsters (IBT), Local 676, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Issue: recall - method of recall.
- C & D Batteries, Div. of Eltra Corp. vs. IAM, Local 632, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Caloric Appliance Corp. vs. Eastern Conference Board of Int'l. Holders & Foundry Workers Union of N.A., Local 114, 1958-1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Capitol Bus Co. vs. Amalgamated. Assoc. of Street, Electric Railways and Motor Coach Employees of Amer., Division 1195, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Issue: vacation pay - discharge.
- Capitol Records, Inc. vs. IAM, Record Lodge 1963, District 128, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Issue: suspensions; overtime - layoff.
- Capitol Tire Co. vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum & Plastic Workers of America, CIO, Local 413 (URW), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Capitol City Publishing Co. vs. Trenton Typographical Union, No. 71, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Issue: overtime - rates of pay.
- Capri Restaurant vs. Waiters & Waitresses Union, Local 301, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Carrier Corp. vs. Sheet Metal Workers Int'l. Assoc, Local 527, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Issue: classification of jobs -rates of pay.
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. vs. UAW, Local 786, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Issue: overtime - failure to schedule; hiring - preferential rights.
- Celanese Corp. of Amer., Celanese Fibers Co. Cases, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Cellucap Manufacturing Co. vs. United Papermakers & Paperworkers, Local 35, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Issue: management rights - pay days.
- Celotex Corp. Cases, 1966-1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Celotex Corp. Cases, 1966-1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Celotex Corp. Cases, 1966-1975 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Center City Cadillac Co. vs. Int'l. Assn. of Machinists, Local 724, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Issue: dismissal for disloyalty.
- Central States Publishing Co. vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  No decision included
- Certain-teed, Saint Gobain Insulation Corp. Cases, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Chamberlain Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of American, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Chein, J. & Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Issue: past practice with regard to shift scheduling.
- Chemical Leaman Tank Lines, Inc. vs. Tank Truck Workers, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Issue: holiday schedules of work; suspension for accident.
- Cherry Hill Chrysler Plymouth, Inc. vs. Teamsters Local Union 676, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Issue: dismissal (no cause listed). Ho decision - lust correspondence & contract between the parties.
- Chesapeake Corporation of Virginia vs. Int'l. Brotherhood. of Pulp, Sulphite & Paper Hill Workers, Local 467, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Issue: unscheduled overtime.
- Chesapeake Motor Lines, Inc. vs. Freight Drivers & Helpers Local 557, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Issue: dismissal for dishonesty.
- Chester-Norton Electronics Corp. Cases, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Chilton Printing Co. vs. Philadelphia Typographical Union, Local 2, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Issue: dismissal/ incompetence
- Cities Service Oil Co. vs. Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers. Int'l. Union, Local 12-538, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Issue: classification of jobs by seniority.
- Clifton Conduit Company vs. IBEW, Local 1644, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Issue: vacation - job eligibility.
- Coleman Enterprise Corp. vs. Upholsterers' Int'l. Union, Local 468, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Issue: dismissal/ unauthorized absence.
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. (WCAV-TV Station) vs. IBEW, Local 1241, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Issue: suspension/abuse of discretion.
- Columbian Carbon Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 670, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Issue: classification of jobs/ added duties, upgrading.
- Congoleum-Narin Inc. vs. UMWA, District 50, Local 12698; vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum & Plastic Workers of America, 1957-1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Connelly Containers, Inc. Cases, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Container Corporation of America vs. IBPSPHW; Continental Can Co. vs. Intl Union of District 50, 1950-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Continental Diamond Fibre Corp. vs. United Textile Workers. of America, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Issue: bumping (seniority); discipline suspension, refusal of overtime.
- Cooperson Brothers vs. IAM, #724, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (absenteeism, intoxication) No award included, only written notes.
- Crane Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood. of Operative Potters, Local 313, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Issue: rates of pay/incentive pay.
- Cross Brothers Heat Packers Inc. vs. Amalgamated Heat Cutters & Butcher Workmen of North American, Local 195, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Issue: discipline - discharge (negligence & carelessness, violation of plant rules).
- Crown Cork & Seal Co., Inc. vs. IAM, Local 1672, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  1) Issue: rates of pay (rate division). 2) Issue: classification of jobs/downgrading. 3) Issue: classification of jobs/downgrading.
- Crown Zellerbach Corp. vs. Newark Printing Specialists & Paper Products Union, Local 730, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Issue: discipline/discharge.
- Cuneo Eastern Press Cases, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Curley Co. Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 8-398, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (leaving plant without permission).
- Curtis Publishing Co. vs. Int'l. Printing Pressman & Assistants Union, Local 749, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Issue: layoff/seniority, failure to observe.
- Curtiss-Wright Corp. vs. UAW, Local 580, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  Issue: classification of jobs/downgrading.
- Cutler Metal Products Co. vs. UERMWA, Local 159, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Issue: discipline/discharge (insubordination).
- Degnan Chevrolet, Inc. vs. Teamsters Union Local 158, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Issue: discharge - commissions - backpay (notes & exhibits).
- Delmarva Power & Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1307, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Issue: discharge - absence - excessive (? exhibits).
- Department of Mental Health of the State of Delaware vs. AFSCME, Local 516 & 640., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Issue: 1) arbitration procedure - multiple grievances. 2) transfer.
- Dewey & Almy Chemical Division of W. R. Grace & Co. vs. Passaic - Bergen Joint Bd., Local 1983, TWVA, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Issue: rates of pay - new machinery.
- Diamond Nat'l. Corp., Diamond Packaging Products Division vs. U.P.P., Local 98, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Issue: discharge - fights & altercations - assault on fellow employee, (notes & exhibits).
- Dixie Cup Division of American Can Co, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  1) Issue: overtime - failure to schedule 2) Issue: seniority - plant wide, departmental seniority. 3) Issue: shift scheduling.
- Dixie Ohio Express, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge No. 804, District 34, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Issue: layoff - holiday pay (notes & exhibits).
- Dodge Steel Co. vs. Int'l. Holders & Foundry Workers Union, Local No. 1, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Issue: quit -involuntary (handwritten draft of award & opinion).
- Doeskin Products, Inc. vs. U.P.P, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Issue: holiday pay - unexcused absence.